{
    "id": "6c67f8bc4fe74e308bc37f8d8ca5ba88",
    "title": "Too And Enough",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There were ……………….. many questions to answer so I ran out of time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is old ………………… to make her own bed now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The tea was ………………….. hot for me to drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The room was …………………. so I turned the heating off.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too enough",
                "hot enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t buy the laptop because it was …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough expensive",
                "too expensive"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The shirt was ………………. so I didn’t buy it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too small",
                "small enough"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The tablet is ……………… to fit inside your pocket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too small",
                "small enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ………………. to start a new lesson now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too late",
                "late enough"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t got …………………. to buy the tickets.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too money",
                "enough money"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ……………… to carry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too light",
                "light enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}